Finding Aid for Thomas B. Buell family papers 1840-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Darius David Buell (1907-1990)
  The Darius David Buell (1907-1990) series (.35 linear feet) is almost entirely correspondence. Darius was a prolific letter writer, particularly in his later years and wrote often to family and friends as well as to newspapers, politicians and corporations. A subseries contains information on Darius' and Charlotte's terms as officers in the township.
  - Business
    - Correspondence 1954-1973 (Box 4)
    - Farm Records 1943-1964 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous 1942, 1954, 1959, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Vincent Roy 1967-1971 (Box 4)
  - Charlotte L. Buell 1973 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence
    - Family and Friends 1963-1978 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous 1943-1949, 1961-1979, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Elmira Politics 1972-1978, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Mary Chappell Buell 1931-1945 (Box 4)
  - Memoir Notes undated (Box 4)
  - Newsclippings 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - St. Thomas Church 1966-1976 (Box 4)
- Topical Files
  The series, Topical Files (.75 linear feet) contains background and historical information on Union City, Elmira and the extended Buell family, most noticeably the Stewart family. This series also contains miscellaneous family correspondence and a folder of essays written by family members and friends.
  - Business Cards undated, 1912, 1937 (Box 4)
  - Elmira
    - Early Elmira Newspaper 1883, photocopy (Box 4)
    - Early Photographs circa 1800, circa 1900, 1987, photocopy (Box 4)
    - Historical Notes of Charlotte Buell, circa 1960 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous undated, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Newsclippings 1983-1995 (Box 4)
    - Polish in Elmira undated, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Essays by Family and Friends 1878, circa 1900 (Box 4)
  - Extended Family History
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence undated, 1917 (Box 4)
    - Stewart Family 1996-1998 (Box 4)
    - Stewart Genealogy undated, 1905 (Box 4)
  - Olivet College undated, 1866-1878, 1944 (Box 4)
  - Union City
    - Directories 1919-1922 (Box 4)
    - First Congregational United Church of Christ 1899, 1909, 1987-1993 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous undated, 1876 (Box 4)
    - Newsclippings 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - Union City Centennial 1966 (Box 4)
    - "Union City on the St. Jo" 1895 (Box 4)
- Photographs
  Portraits of family members; group photos of Olivet College students, ca. 1876 and of University of Michigan Delta Tau Delta party, ca. 1901; snapshots of family farm in Elmira, Michigan and of farming activities.
  - Portraits of family members, 2 envelopes (Box 4)
  - Family farm and farming activities, Elmira, Michigan (Box 4)
  - College groups, family reunion (Box 4)